Fahhad Rajper

Photographer and Graphic Designer with experience of over 8 years, specialized in fashion/e.com photography and content design, competent in capturing high quality images, copy writing and creating engaging designs while displaying confidence and professionalism at all times.



EXPERIENCE

<u>Prestij Consulting</u>, Istanbul, Turkiye — Content Creator

November 2023 - Present

Producing engaging and high-quality materials across various mediums for international and Turkish audiences in english. Including video, photography, written content, design and social media creatives.

YBM Interieurs, Karachi — Photographer/Social Media Manager

August 2016 - Present (Remote)

Designing social media monthly calendar including annual print portfolio, PR package designs, content creation (photography and videography) of engaging content to reach relevant audiences and providing online customer assistance to increase foot fall.

Freelancer — Photographer

October 2014 - October 2023

Developing mood boards, retouching photos, set design arrangements Indoor and outdoor fashion shoot, product, portrait, food, interior and architecture, events and travel photography services.

Brandverse, Karachi, Pakistan — Fashion Photographer

October 2019 - January 2021

In-house fashion photographer providing services to all relevant fashion related clients, mainly e.com photography, creating mood boards to directing shoots and guiding junior photographers.

Westeros Café, Karachi —Co-Founder

November 2017 - January 2019

As a Managing Partner; Oversaw all aspects of business from content development, marketing to developing recipes to hiring and guiding kitchen staff. Including creative aspects, and customer service processes.

Helession, Athen, Greece — Intern

February 2016 - April 2016

AIESEC exchange program; Social Media management & content design for English speaking clients and communicating with potential consumers at the exhibition .

CONTACT

Phone: +90-541-4847634 Whatsapp: +90-541-4847634 Email: fahhadrajper@gmail.com Portfolio: www.fahhadrajper.com

LOCATION

Istanbul, Turkiye

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop

Graphic Design

Canva

ChatGPT

Videography

Video Editing

Orbitvu Photography

LANGUAGES

English

Sindhi

Urdu

Hindi

Siraiki

EDUCATION

Bahria Foundation, Naushehro Feroze — *Matriculation*

D.A Degree, Karachi — Intermediate

Karachi University, Karachi — B.Com

Arena Multimedia, Karachi — Diploma in Graphic Design

PROJECTS

#TryBeatingMeLightly — Social Media Campaign

This Project Photographic work was a campaign in response to the bill that CII proposed in the National Assembly, which proposed legalisation of Men beating their wives "Lightly". #TryBeatingMeLightly was featured on platforms like BBC, Times Magazine, Buzzfeed (World Wide), Voice of America, ToI and many more.

Khaadi Webstore — E.com Revamp

In my time at <u>Brandverse</u>, I demonstrated proficient skills in revamping Khaadi's Fashion Ecommerce (2020) shoot by utilizing effective techniques ranging from mood board creation to seamless execution, resulting in a remarkable increase of articles from 60 to 138 within a time span of 6 hours, leveraging Orbitvu elevated photography while working with multiple models.

YBM Oud — Product Packaging Design / Launch

Single-handedly spearheaded the entire process of YBM Oud product development, ranging from the meticulous selection of premium-quality oud wood chips to the innovative packaging design, as well as the seamless execution of the product photoshoot and successful launch. This outstanding achievement has led to <u>YBM</u> Oud maintaining its position as the top-selling oud brand to date.

Prestij Consulting — Social Media Revamp

<u>Prestij Consulting's</u> comprehensive revamp of social media design to elevate brand's aesthetic and increase engagement. This included implementing visually appealing graphics, animation, optimizing layout and typography, and leveraging consistent branding across all platforms. Additionally, creation of a podcast to showcase the properties unique features and benefits. The result was a significant increase in our social media following, as well as a boost in sales and brand awareness.